http://www.tribeofjudah.com/tojmm/privacy-policy/

Tribe of Judah Motorcycle MinistriesNavigationHomeAbout UsBen PriestTammy PriestHistoryPastor Ben’s BlogWe BelieveInvite Ben PriestJesusWho is He?Prayer of SalvationPrayers for LifePrayer RequestsTen Benefits of God’s FavorShare Praise ReportsGet InvolvedMediaAudioVideoPhoto GalleryAround the WorldBeginningsHistory MakersRace TeamEventsReunion in the Rockies 2009Family Reunion 2012Spina BifidaDental VanBiker BaptismWomen of GodYouth ForceArticlesMe & My MotorcycleYour Word NOWReal PeopleReal StoriesMember ProfilePartnershipPartner LetterDonationsHarvest PartnersMillennium Messengers4th Man TeamFaith ProjectsBen’s Life Story BookMedia UpgradesMen of Faith Resident HouseOutreach Facility UpgradesTOJ Outreach BiblesKroger ProgramLife StoreContactPrivacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Tribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministry collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the www.tribeofjudah.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Tribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministry.Personal identification informationWe may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.Non-personal identification informationWe may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.Web browser cookiesOur Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.How we use collected informationTribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministry may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:- To process payments
We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.- To send periodic emails
We may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.How we protect your informationWe adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures.Sharing your personal informationWe do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.Changes to this privacy policyTribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministry has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.Your acceptance of these termsBy using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.Contacting usIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:
Tribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministry
www.tribeofjudah.com
PO Box 2423 Humble, TX 77347
(281) 358-7770
toj@tribeofjudah.comThis document was last updated on June 14, 2013 Tribe of Judah Int’l HeadquartersRiver of God Church
PO Box 2423
Humble, TX
77347
Phone (281) 358-7770
Fax (281) 358-7771
Email toj@tribeofjudah.com Like Us Tribe of Judah MMRiver of God ChurchSundays 10:00am
Wednesdays 7:00pmEveryone Welcome Like Us River of God ChurchTOJ Member LoginClick Here to LoginMember Access RequestCopyright © 2020 Tribe of Judah Motorcycle Ministries. All Rights Reserved - Privacy Policy
